Prepare to catch feelings.
Sidelined: The QB and Me is a comedy, romance film directed by Justin Wu.
Dallas, a burdened but headstrong dancer, is determined to get into the best
dance school in the country—her late mother’s alma mater.
However, that dream is suddenly derailed when the cheeky yet secretly grieving football
star, Drayton, crashes into her life with a unique story of his own.
Will the two of them be able to grow into their dreams
together, or will their dreams be sidelined?
Dallas Bryan, played by Siena Agudong.
Drayton Lahey, played by Noah Beck.
Nathan Bryan, played by Drew Ray Tanner.
Leroy Lahey, played by James Van Der Beek.
Miss Alicia, played by Deborah Cox.
Gabby, played by Asia Lizardo.
Siena Nicole Agudong (born August 19,  2004) is an American actress.
On television, she is known for her roles in the Nickelodeon series Star Falls (2018),
and the Netflix series No Good Nick (2019) and Resident Evil (2022).
Her films include Alex & Me (2018), Upside-Down Magic (2020), Kevin Smith's
The 4:30 Movie (2024), and Sidelined: The QB and Me (2024).
The film explores themes of high school, based on novel or book,
american football player, based on web novel.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.